[ electronic music playing ]
[ hip-hop music blaring ]
Duckett ! Answer your phone .
My messages are delivering , so I know you 're fuckin ' seeing ' em .
Yo . Seen Duckett ?
Uh , yeah , he 's inside . He 's fucking off his head .
Bro , he 's definitely on something , eh ?
[ cheering and hollering ]
Hey , is Duckett up there ?
[ boy 2 ] Who the fuck is Duckett ? [ laughs ]
[ hip-hop music continues ]
- Oi ! Any of you seen Duckett ? - [ girl ] ] No , I haven 't !
Oi . Oi , seen Duckett ?
[ muttering nonchalantly ]
Cole ! Get your brother under control .
- Where is he ? - He 's in Jayden 's room . Go .
[ thumping on door ]
Dude , what 's your brother 's deal ?
Duckett ! Open the door , man ! I 'm not screwing around .
Mate , I 'm this close to calling the cops .
Duckett , open the door or I 'll break it down .
- [ Duckett ] Go away , Cole ! - What ?
Dude , what the hell ? You 're gonna break my mum 's door !
Nah , fuck this !
- Cole 's breaking my fuckin ' ... - Duckett .
[ Duckett ] Can you see them ? They 're in here .
[ Cole ] I 'm gonna take you home . Okay , bro ?
[ Duckett ] Pop said you 're gonna hurt a lot of people .
[ Cole sighs ]
Pop 's dead , Duckett .
- You 're not him . - What are you talking about ?
[ boy 3 ] Bro , look at Duckett . He 's fucked !
Are you serious ?
Put your phones down !
[ murmuring ]
Put your fuckin ' phones away !
- [ boy 4 ] Hey , hey , bro ... - Everyone fuck off !
[ knife scrapes ]
- [ music stops ] - [ all gasp and scream ]
- [ boy 5 ] It 's a knife ! - [ all clamoring ]
[ feedback whines over speakers ]
[ screaming ]
[ melancholy music playing ]
[ indistinct playful chatter playing through earphones ]
[ girl on recording ] What are you doing ?
[ chatter continues ]
Get off me . Get off ! [ laughs ]
- Mum ! - [ recording stops ]
[ man ] Sorry .
No , I am . I just needed a moment .
- Your aunty wants to talk to you . - Yeah , okay .
[ aunty Lee ] I 've still got her name in contacts .
You know ... I should - - I should take her out , but I just can 't do it .
Yeah , me neither .
You thought about what you 're gonna do when you finish school ?
[ Mia ] Hmm ...
Work with your dad ? [ chuckles ]
[ chuckles ]
[ faucet running ]
[ sneezes , sniffles ]
[ Max ] You getting a cold , Mi ?
[ faucet stops ]
- What ? - You getting a cold ?
Uh , yeah , I think so .
[ faucet runs ]
How was today for you ?
- [ faucet stops ] - What ?
Fine .
[ cell phone ringing and vibrating ]
- Hey . - [ boy on phone ] Hey , Mia .
- Can you come pick me up ? - Oh , okay , now ?
- Where 'd you go ? - I was on the phone .
My sister was meant to be picking me up .
My fat mum 's meant to pick me up . She 's probably off eating dick somewhere .
[ both chuckle ]
- Is that Alex ? - Yeah , his Snapchats are so cringe .
He looks like my mum in half of ' em .
- He looks Elvish . - What 's Elvish ?
You know , like the fantasy elves .
Shut up .
I swear he stole one of my cigarettes .
You smoke now ?
Nah , I just sell ' em . I sold , like , two to him today .
He 's such a try hard .
He invited me to his house to hang .
- I thought you hated him . - Eh .
Do you reckon they give you cancer straightaway ?
I don 't know . Don 't smoke it ?
Don 't tell me what to do .
Here you go .
Nah . I hate the smell .
You 're a fuckin ' fetus .
I need a new best mate .
[ car approaching ]
Riley !
You little feral . Cigarettes ?
- We weren 't actually smoking them . - He 's lying , Mia .
He 's already had half a packet .
Need a lift anywhere ?
Nah , Mum 's gonna get here soon . Thanks , though .
All right . Well , just call Riley if she doesn 't rock up .
All right , thanks .
Yeah , and have fun with your cancer .
- See ya , Mia . See ya , fetus ! - [ car door opens , closes ]
both singing along 10 stereo ) ♪ I 'm gonna swing ♪
$ From the chandelier ♪
♪ I 'm ? ♪
♪ Gonna live ♪
♪ Like tomorrow doesn 't exist ♪
♪ Like it doesn 't ... ♪
Whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa .
♪ I 'm ♪
♪ Gonna fly like a ... ♪
[ switches off stereo ]
Um ... stay in the car , okay ?
[ animal grunting ]
- [ animal groans ] - Oh , shit .
- You poor thing . - [ Riley ] What do we do ?
[ kangaroo groaning ]
Do we call a vet ?
That 's not gonna help , Riley . I mean , look at it .
Well , we can 't just leave it like that .
[ kangaroo groans ]
Can you at least put it out of its misery ?
[ kangaroo bellows ]
Okay .
[ car doors close ]
[ car engine starts ]
- [ tires squeal ] - [ engine revs ]
[ tires screech ]
[ kangaroo grunts ]
[ grunting continues ]
Mia , no , we can 't leave it like this .
Another car will come .
Mia , it 's crying .
- [ uneasy music playing ] - [ kangaroo groans ]
[ mellow music playing through earphones ]
- [ thump ] - Oh !
- Hey ! - [ Mia laughs ]
What the hell ? Love it when you rock up uninvited .
Love it when you forget to pick up Riley .
Ow !
I 'm sorry . I had you on mute .
Ah , cool story . I 'm telling Mum .
- No , you 're not ! - Yes , I am !
Thanks for picking him up , Mi .
All good . Come on , Cookie . Oh , God , you stink !
Oh , you 're a smelly girl !
[ grunts ]
[ sighs ]
[ typing on cell phone ]
Saw a dying kangaroo .
What ?
On the side of the road . It was in so much pain .
Why didn 't you call the RSPCA ?
I dunno .
It was almost dead .
I wanted to put it out of its misery .
Thanks for ignoring my calls , by the way .
I haven 't been ignoring your calls . I 've been busy .
Uh , yeah , busy ignoring me .
[ " Crazy Frog " ringtone plays ]
- No , Jade , don 't . Don 't ! - What ?
Don 't answer it ! I let a kangaroo suffer .
- Daniel ... - I need consoling !
[ Daniel on phone ] Is that Mia ?
- I 'll call you back , yeah ? - Okay , sure .
Okay , bye .
- Bye ! Bye , Daniel ! Bye ! - [ laughs ]
[ groans ] All right . I 'm consoling you .
- Have you seen the group chat ? - You mean the one I invited you to ?
[ Mia ] It 's Hayley 's video . They 're doing it again tonight .
- No , Mia . - I want to see if it 's real !
No , not tonight , Mia . I can 't .
[ shouting and hollering on recording ]
[ switches phone off ]
It was Mum 's two years .
That was today ?
Yeah .
I just want to forget about it .
And ... I need Daniel to come give my Gucci some attention .
- [ Jade groans ] - [ Mia laughs ]
Enough ! Daniel 's not touching your Gucci , Mia !
Hey , he was my boyfriend before he was yours .
You guys held hands once three years ago . That doesn 't mean anything .
Jade , it 's my Mum 's remembrance day . Please ?
[ Jade sighs ]
Daniel can come , too , yeah ?
If he 's touching my Gucci , yes .
- Stop ! - [ both laugh ]
[ " Crazy Frog " ringtone plays ]
- Can you give me five minutes ? - What am I gonna do for five minutes ?
Oh , I don 't know . Wash Cookie or something !
I don 't wanna wash Cookie !
Oh , fine ! I will babysit Riley , the better sibling .
Do not talk about your Gucc ♪ with Riley , please .
He has got to learn ! The boy 's got to learn !
- Bye . - Miss you already . Bye .
- Love you . - [ Jade chuckles ]
[ sighs ]
[ door opens ]
" Can I help ? "
" Yes , Riley , thank you for asking . "
Need a hand ?
I 'm sorry I couldn 't get to your mum 's thing .
- I couldn 't get off work . - No , it 's fine .
How 's your dad ?
Oh , hey ...
You can be honest .
I hate being around him . He 's so depressing .
I 'm a bad person , Sue . Can you fix me ?
You 're not broken , Mia .
- [ sneezes ] - Whoa . Okay .
Ugh , God , I 'm dying .
- It 's just a cold . You 'll kick it . - Thank you .
Riley , get your shit off the table .
Did you hear me ?
- Yes , Mum , I 'm coming . - Okay .
[ muttering indistinctly ]
- Mum ? You going to bed ? - You sneaking out ?
Why do you always think I 'm sneaking out or I 'm sleeping around ?
Because you only ask if I 'm going to bed when you 're sneaking out .
Is it to see Daniel ?
You know , even if it was , he 's ultra-Christian .
- He doesn 't do anything ever . - He 's still got a dick , Jade .
- Is it him you 're sneaking out to see ? - I 'm not sneaking out !
Okay .
[ mutters ] God . Night .
Lock the door on your way out .
[ footsteps receding ]
- Are we sneaking out now ? - Shh !
- [ Sue ] Bye , Mia . - Oh , my God !
Right , I 'm sorry .
What ? I didn 't do anything .
- What are you doing ? - Mia said I could come .
How could I say no to him ?
- You 're not coming . - All right , then , I 'll tell Mum .
Yeah , well , she pretty much already knows .
What , about you not picking me up ?
[ sighs ] Whatever .
- Yo , check this out . - [ commotion on recording ]
- I swear it 's fake . - Mm , I don 't know .
- It 's 1,000 % a trick . - How would Hayley fake that ?
- Why would they ? - Why would they ?
They 're an attention whore . They 're trying to get everyone to go to their house
and talk about them and you 've fallen for it .
- [ Mia ] Sorry for ruining your phone date . - Apology not accepted .
You 're gonna be pregnant by next month , I swear .
Pregnant ? He hasn 't even kissed me yet .
What ? You guys have been going out for , like , three months .
- What is that ? - Even I 've kissed Jazzie .
[ scoffs ] The girl with the horse mouth ? You shouldn 't be kissing horses , Riley .
♪ I 'm like the Jay or the Drake of my city ♪
♪ Fuck what they say , they won 't say that shit to me ♪
♪ I 'm in downtown all my brothers is with me ♪
Only an hour late . Great .
Been waiting for Mum to sleep .
Oh , and we are babysitting too , apparently .
[ song continues ]
Fuck me .
♪ Drive through the hood in Lamborghini cars ♪
♪ I might just give a hunnid to my dawgs
♪ Thank you for holding it down ♪
♪ And I 'm sorry if you ever felt like there was love lost ♪
♪ Now they blamin ' ONEFOUR for all of the drillings ♪
♪ They blamin ' us for what happens in Sydney ♪
♪ They blamin ' us for what happens in Melbourne ♪
♪ They blamin ' us for what happens in Brissy ... ♪
Yo . What 's up ?
Just chillin ' .
Cool .
[ indistinct chatter and laughter ]
Sick house , Joss .
Yeah .
Oh ... nah , it 'll pick up soon , I 'm sure .
[ boy ] How you doin ' , man ?
[ laughing ]
[ ' Spot the Difference " by Onefour and The Kid LAROI continues ]
Boop !
You all good ?
Yeah , just ...
being weird .
You 're not being weird . You just need to loosen up .
Brr !
Yeah , just do that . It looks incredibly normal .
- [ both ] Brr ! - [ laughing ]
- Just do that . Brr ! - [ door opens ]
- Hey , Mia , brr ! [ laughs ] - Fuck , I love you .
- Jade ! - Daniel !
[ Daniel ] Finally .
Um , hi , ex-boyfriend !
[ all moan cheerily ]
- [ Daniel ] Group hug . - Hold me , ex-boyfriend .
I am lonely . I am so , so lonely !
You right there , woman ?
- I 'm sorry for dragging you out . - Nah . I wasn 't doing anything .
I actually wanted to get out of the house for a bit .
[ clears throat ] Wanna come grab a drink ?
I don 't wanna do it . [ laughs ]
- They want you to do it . - I don 't wanna do it .
[ Jade groans ]
How you been ?
- Dude , why 'd you have to bring her ? - [ Daniel ] How you going , man ?
- Good . You ? - Yeah , good , thanks .
First , uh , big boys ' party , huh ?
[ Riley ] I don 't really know anyone .
You 're gonna know everyone by the end of the night .
Oh , good .
- She 's fine . - No , she 's not fine .
- She irritates the fuck out of me . - She 's literally done nothing to you .
She 's so clingy , man . It 's fucking depressing .
Oh ! Now she 's flirting with your boy .
They 're friends , Hayley .
Keep telling yourself that .
All right , let 's do this !
[ all cheering and whooping ]
[ Jade ] Yeah , let 's fake another video .
[ hoot ]
[ boy ] Oh , I 've been waiting for this shit !
Be pretty sick to hook the kid up .
- He 's not doing anything , Joss . - Ah , come on , Jade .
- Imagine it , though . - Joss , I said no .
All right . More for me .
Thank you sir .
- [ Joss ] I guess , uh , I 'll go first and ... - [ Hayley ] Nah , man , you always go first .
- Well , it 's my house . - It 's my fuckin ' hand .
- Duckett gave it to me . - Joss , you 're a fucking hog !
Look , does anyone else want to volunteer ?
I 'll do it .
- You wanna do it ? - Mm-hmm .
- Wanna do it ? - Yeah .
- Do you wanna do it ? - [ cheers and whoops ]
[ hooting and hollering ]
Sit down , Mia .
- [ girl ] Better her than me . - Tie her .
Yes , sir . Hands up .
Mm , Kinky .
What are we playing ?
It 's nothing , Riley . Hayley 's tricked everyone .
[ Hayley ] All right , somebody time it .
As soon as she lets it in , it cannot go for more than 90 seconds .
Am I clear ?
What happens after 90 seconds ?
They 'll want to stay .
[ sinister music playing ]
And if you die while they 're in you ,
well , they 'll have you forever .
[ both laugh ]
[ Mia ] So lame .
Hey , I 'm just relaying what I 've been told , okay ?
Oh ! Fuck , dude !
Trust me ... it 's gotta be tight .
Candles ?
Light the candle to open the door .
Blow it out to close it .
[ murmuring ]
Okay , Mia .
[ ominous music playing ]
Ah ...
Put your hand on it .
[ cell phone pings ]
No , like , hold it .
Now say ...
" Talk to me . "
Talk to me .
- [ ominous musical sting ] - [ gasps ]
[ all laugh ]
Oh , my God !
Oh , my God , what the fuck ?
[ laughter continues ]
Who the fuck was that ?
Who was that ?
I dunno , man . It 's different every time . [ laughs ]
- [ boy ] Hey , you signed up . - Where 'd he go ?
Mia , stop .
No , you didn 't do it right . You gotta say , " I let you in . "
- No , I 'm flipping out . - [ Jade ] Seriously , Mia , shut up .
No , someone was sitting there , I swear to fuck .
Okay , I 'm proving it .
[ Hayley ] Attagirl , prove it ! Prove it . That 's right , say it .
- [ sinister music playing ] - [ Mia breathing heavily ]
[ all chanting ] Do it . Do it .
Do it . Do it .
- Do it . - [ laughs and squeals ]
Do it ! Do it ! Do it ! Do it ! Do it !
[ chanting and shouting continue ]
- Okay ! Okay . Okay . - [ all quiet ]
[ exhales heavily ]
Talk to me .
[ whimpers ]
[ Hayley ] Hey , hey , don 't let go , Mia . Do not let go .
I can 't look at it !
You don 't have to look at it ! Just say it .
- I can 't ! - Say it !
[ distorted breathing ]
[ Hayley ] I let you in . I let you in .
I let you in .
[ gasps ]
[ dissonant soundscape ]
- [ Joss ] Someone timing it ? - [ Hayley ] Got it .
There you are .
Shh . Shh-shh-shh-shh .
[ Mia groaning softly ]
[ all laughing ]
[ Mia groaning ]
[ Mia laughs ]
[ laughs maniacally ]
[ gulps ]
- [ gasps ] - [ water splashes ]
[ groaning softly ]
[ in gravelly monotone ] There he is .
[ breathes raspingly ]
[ in gravelly monotone ] They like you .
[ all snickering ]
What ?
[ barks sharply ]
Oh , shit ! Not you , though .
[ laughter ]
[ gasps , gulps ]
- [ moans , inhales ] - [ water splashes ]
- [ strained breathing ] - [ boy ] Whoa .
[ door creaking ]
[ all screaming and clamoring ]
[ clamoring subsides ]
[ girl ] Yeah , Mia !
[ in gravelly monotone ] He 's behind you now .
[ ominous music playing ]
He 'll split ya , pretty boy .
He 'll split ya !
Eighty-three seconds . Joss , get it off her .
- All right , you 've had enough . - He 'll split ya .
[ grunts ] He 'll split ya . He 'll split ya .
[ Joss strains ]
- [ Joss grunts ] - [ thuds ]
[ maniacally ] Run . Run .
Run . Run . Run .
Run . Run .
Run ! Run ! Run ! Run ! Run ! Run !
- Run ! Run ! Run ! Run ! Run ! - Ninety seconds , for fuck sake !
Run ! Run ! Run ! Run ! Run ! Run ! Run ! Run !
Run ! Run ! Run ! Run ! Run !
- [ screams ] Run ! - [ shouting ]
Hey . Hey . You okay ?
We went a bit over .
Hey .
[ gasping ]
[ panting heavily ]
[ in normal voice ] That was ...
amazing !
[ all cheering and whooping ]
That was the best one yet !
[ cheering and screaming ]
[ laughs ]
- [ breathing heavily ] - [ hooting continues ]
- [ thunder rumbling ] - [ rain pattering ]
[ thundering continues ]
[ thunder crashing ]
[ whispers ] Jade . Jade , are you up ?
You 're not sleeping in here .
- I didn 't even ask that . - Isn 't that what you want ?
No . I 'm just bored .
Look , Riley , you 're not nine anymore , all right ?
[ Cookie panting ]
Goodnight .
Can you shut the door ?
[ thunder rumbling ]
Shut the door !
- Sook ! - [ door slams shut ]
What a bitch .
- Can I hang with you ? - It 's your house , bro .
Did the hand thing scare you ?
A bit .
You gonna have nightmares , Riley ?
I don 't get nightmares .
I do .
Like what ?
I have this reoccurring nightmare ...
where ...
I 'm looking in the mirror and my reflection is gone .
Like I don 't exist .
What did the hand feel like ?
Hmm ...
It felt amazing .
I felt like I was glowing .
I could hear and see and feel everything .
But I was in the passenger seat .
It felt incredible .
Hmm .
How did your mum die ?
You know .
Only bits .
She , uh ...
took too many sleeping pills . By accident .
Dad was sleeping on the couch .
In the morning , he couldn 't open the door .
Hmm .
Why ?
Mum was on the other side .
And there were scratches on the door and wood under her nails .
She tried to get help , but she couldn 't .
Jade said you got depression after .
I was just feeling alone .
No , you can 't ever be alone " cause you 'll always have me and Jade .
Yeah .
It 's okay , I don 't feel alone anymore .
[ thunder rumbling ]
[ thunder and rain continue ]
[ man ] Wait . Oh , my God ...
- Is it being constipated ? - Are you fuckin ' ...
He 's won a million pounds !
- [ cheering and applause ] - [ laughter and excited shouting ]
- [ video stops playing ] - [ rain pattering gently ]
[ ominous music playing ]
- [ school bell rings ] - [ indistinct chatter ]
[ indistinct announcement over PA ]
- You busy tonight ? - You want a turn , eh ?
No . Daniel does .
What 's in it for me ?
My company .
- That 's pretty cool , I reckon . - [ chuckles ]
No , we can 't go to Jose 's . His place is trashed . He 's pissed .
My house , then .
I 've got a party later . I 've gotta be gone by 11 : 00 .
- Mum leaves at 9 : 00 , so ... - See ya at 10 : 00 .
Jog on .
[ both squeal excitedly ]
- [ Daniel ] Yes ? - [ Mia ] Yes !
[ knocking at door ]
Hi . Is Jade home ?
[ sighs softly ]
[ mellow music playing ]
- Why is Daniel at the door ? - Mum , can you let him in ?
You 'd better not be having a party , Jade , I swear to God .
It 's two friends . Can you let him in ?
[ sighs softly ]
What time 's everyone getting here ?
- Getting here for what ? - The party .
- Is there a party tonight ? - Don 't bullshit me .
I 'm ... I 'm sorry ...
Have you got alcohol in your car ?
Oh , no . I don 't drink , so ...
You 're good .
[ footsteps receding ]
What time 's the party again ?
- What party ? - The party .
Jade told me . It 's okay . What time ?
Mum , I honestly don 't know what you 're talking about .
- The party tonight . What time is it ? - There 's no party , Mum .
You are not drinking tonight . On God , I will punch you in the face .
Are you drunk ?
James .
If there 's a party , I 'm definitely drinking at it .
Is that Cookie or you , James ? Will you crack a window ?
Jesus , Mum . Knock much ?
Mia , if there is a party tonight ,
you are banned from this house , effective immediately .
Okay ...
So , what , you 're just here third-wheeling for the night , are you ?
It 's really humiliating when you put it that way .
You 'd better not be getting stoned again , Mia .
Oh , my God ! Why does your mum have to know everything ?
- I know everything . - I tried weed one time .
You . My daughter 's vagina ... prohibited .
Oh , my God , Mum ! Leave the room before I kill everyone .
The neighbors tell me everything .
- [ Jade ] Oh , my God ... - Watch it !
- Shut the door . Mum ! - I 'm leaving it open !
- I 'm so sorry . - Ooh . That 's embarrassing .
♪ I saw your face ♪
♪ Displayed upon a crescent moon ♪
♪ That wavers up and down depending how the petals bloom ♪
♪ Doomed , always destitute , fused through infected roots ♪
♪ Searching for a message ♪
♪ But there 's nowhere left to exit to ... ♪
Riley !
- Mia ! - Mm ! You keen ?
I said don 't smoke in my house .
Mm !
[ song continues ]
Hmm ... nice place .
That 's an ugly fuckin ' dog .
Excuse me .
- I 'm thirsty . - [ bottles clink ]
So , where 'd you get it from , anyway ?
[ Joss ] I 'll tell you what it is , right ?
It 's the hand of a psychic .
Got cut off and embalmed . Legit .
It 's a medium , Joss . Not a psychic .
- Yeah , this isn 't an embalmed hand . - Yes , it is , Danny boy .
See , look . The ceramic shit is put over it .
But if you smash it , there 's an actual hand in there .
- You 're full of shit . - I 'm serious . [ chuckles ]
Apparently , it was the hand of someone who could connect with the dead , right ,
so everyone around him thought , " Let 's just cut his hand off . "
- White people shit , man , I tell ya . - [ all chuckle ]
Oi , I heard it was the hand of a satanist .
The other hand 's just out there somewhere .
Out where ? Shut up , all right ?
- Fuckin ' make me ! - You just talk shit . [ laughs ]
All right .
- [ Daniel ] Where 'd you buy it ? - [ Joss ] Oh , nah , I didn 't buy it .
A friend gave it to a friend and ... yeah .
- Who ? - What do you want , Daniel ?
You want a fuckin ' spreadsheet with a transaction history or what ?
- Just hold the hand , say " Talk to me " ... - Okay .
... and ask the spirit your fuckin ' questions , all right ?
This is such bullshit .
Oi , Riley , get the lights .
- [ Daniel ] Film me ? - [ light switches flick ]
- [ Jade ] Yep . - Oi , time it .
[ clears throat ] Okay , champ .
You know the drill .
[ exhales ]
- [ Hayley ] Say it . - [ cell phone pings ]
Talk to me .
Whoa !
[ laughing ] Oh , what ?
- [ all chuckle ] - No way !
- Mate , I don 't have all day . - No . No ...
[ James ] What is it ?
[ exhales sharply ]
Okay . Okay .
Okay .
[ exhales ] Okay , come on .
Okay , come on .
[ breathing heavily ]
I let you in .
[ gasps ]
- [ choking ] - [ chair rattling ]
Hayley , he 's choking .
Hold it .
[ choking ]
Hayley , fucking stop it ! He 's choking !
Hold it .
[ choking ]
[ sighs ]
There we go . [ laughs ]
[ giggles ]
[ all chuckling ]
[ gentle creaking ]
[ sinister music playing ]
[ croakily ] He hates it when you touch him .
You make him soft .
- [ whispers ] Yo , this spirit 's a cunt . - [ Daniel moans ]
[ moans ]
[ moaning heavily ]
[ breathing heavily ]
[ heavy breathing continues ]
[ heavy breathing intensifies ]
- [ laughing ] Oh , fuck ! - Oh , shit .
[ giggling ]
[ breathing heavily ]
[ all gasp ]
[ moaning loudly ]
[ both ] Oh !
[ all exclaim and groan in disgust ]
[ Mia ] Oh , no ! I can 't watch !
[ groans and laughs ]
[ screams in disgust ]
- [ all laugh ] - [ Daniel splutters ]
- [ Hayley ] Oh , fuck ! - [ Jade ] You okay ?
Untie me .
[ coughs ] Untie me , come on .
I am , I am . You all right ?
Delete it .
- [ both laughing ] - Delete it , come on !
Yeah , nuh !
Hayley , please . Hayley ...
- [ laughing ] - Post that shit . Post that shit .
Daniel .
[ laughter subsides ]
Guys .
[ Hayley clears throat ]
Oh , yeah , that was , uh ... that was pretty heavy , eh ?
Yeah . You up for it ?
[ Hayley and Joss chuckle ]
Can I have a go ?
- [ Hayley laughing ] Sorry ... - After that ?
Just get your thot dog out and no cameras .
[ ' La Foule " by Edith Piaf playing ]
- [ Mia laughs ] - [ Hayley ] Hey !
[ veils ]
Let 's fucking go !
[ music continues ]
[ gasps ]
- [ shouts nonsensically ] - [ laughing ]
[ all ] ] Mia ! Mia !
[ gasps ]
[ mutters nonsensically ]
[ Mia screams , laughs ]
[ Mia screams ]
[ gasps ]
- [ gasps ] - [ cries out ]
Time 's up , time 's up !
[ barks , laughs ]
♪ Et la joie eclaboussee par son soutrire ♪
♪ Me transperce et rejaillit au fond de moi ♪
♪ Mais soudain je pousse un cri parmi les rires ♪
$ Quand la Foule vient ♪
♪ L 'arracher d 'entre mes bras ...
[ barks ]
[ all chanting ] Talk to me ! Talk to me !
[ cheering and hollering ]
[ gasps ]
[ snarls ]
[ whimpering ]
What the fuck ?
[ song ends ]
[ Joss panting ]
[ chuckling ]
Oh , fuck , yeah . This shit never gets old .
Let 's go ! [ grunts ]
- I need a shot . - [ Riley ] Me , too .
- [ Jade ] No way . - [ James ] Come on , Jade .
You 're not my mum . You 're not even 18 .
- And you 're not even 15 . - So what ?
- [ Riley ] Jade , please . - Riley , I said no .
Fuck sakes .
What if we did it for , like , 60 seconds ?
- Mia , stop . - Sixty seconds , Jade .
You don 't have to be a bitch about all things Riley .
[ Riley ] Yeah , Jade .
You 're just so busy trying to suck Daniel 's dick ,
you don 't give a shit about anybody else .
- [ Joss ] Damn . - Oi , no .
Why do you want to do it so much ? To impress James ?
To come into my room crying that you 're scared , like last time ?
Did you tell your little friend that ?
I hate you .
Like you 're my favorite person in the world .
Can 't help you , bro . Your sister 's fuckin ' boring .
[ chuckles ]
[ Joss ] Oh , shit , oh ...
[ door opens ]
- We should go . - Yes sir .
- [ door closes ] - Sixty seconds . Please .
I dunno , maybe it 's not a good idea .
I actually thought you were gonna be on my side for once .
Hey ... I 'm on both of your sides .
- Obviously not . - Riley ...
Sixty seconds . Please .
Please .
Okay .
- What about 507 - Okay . 50 .
Fifty seconds ?
- Yeah , just get it over with . - Sign the form , baby !
- Let 's go ! - Yeah , boy ! [ laughs ]
[ Joss ] Okay , hold up , hold up .
Hands up .
- [ Hayley ] You all right , kiddo ? - Yeah .
Okay . Let 's do this .
[ Joss ] Riley ... gettin ' crazy !
You know what to say , boy .
- You better not cry after 20 seconds . - I 'll time it .
Talk to me .
[ under breath ] What the fuck ?
Riley .
It 's okay .
Just say it .
[ breathes deeply ]
I let you in .
[ Riley choking ]
Oh , shit .
[ choking continues ]
[ stops choking ]
I 'm so sorry .
I didn 't mean to hurt you .
I 'd never want to hurt you .
I miss you so ...
so much , Mi .
[ tense music playing ]
I didn 't want you to hate me .
Mum ?
Hey , that 's 50 seconds .
No , no . Please don 't close it off .
- Mia ... - It 's my mum . Please .
I love you both , baby .
I love you , too , Mum .
I 'm so proud of you .
[ melancholy music playing ]
And I got ...
got ... got ... got ...
[ choking ] ... got , got , got ...
got , got , got , got ,
got , got , got , got ...
[ Riley chokes , gurgles ]
[ inhales raspingly ]
[ gasps ]
Oh , my God .
- [ heavy bang ] - [ menacing music playing ]
No ! No , no , Riley !
- [ Riley shrieks ] - [ screaming ] Riley , stop !
- [ all clamoring ] - Joss , fucking help me !
Get it off him , Joss !
[ frantic screaming , commotion ]
[ glass shatters ]
- [ gasps ] - [ Daniel ] Oh , my God .
[ menacing music builds ]
Riley ! Riley !
[ screams ]
Fucking help me !
[ Joss ] Oi , help , help , help !
Okay , I 'm gonna untie him ...
- [ Hayley ] Get him on his side ... - [ Jade ] Daniel , call an ambulance !
[ Joss ] No , no , no , no , no , no !
[ voices muffle and fade ]
[ eerie discordant music playing ]
[ Joss ] James , James , get the fuckin ' bag ! Hurry up !
[ muffled voices continue distantly ]
[ breathing heavily ]
- [ Joss ] Where are you going ? - [ Hayley ] We gotta bounce .
- No , we can 't . - We gotta get out of here .
The police are already sus about the Duckett stabbing .
They 're gonna pin this on us . We let them both do the hand , Joss .
We can 't just pretend we weren 't here .
We 're fucked . We 're fucked if ... [ speaking indistinctly ]
[ Joss ] We gotta get our story straight and make sure everyone sticks to it .
Don 't bring up the hand .
[ breathing heavily ]
[ eerie discordant music continues ]
[ faint scratching ]
[ distantly ] Excuse me . We need to talk now , please .
[ line ringing ]
- [ Jade ] Mum , Riley 's in hospital . - [ Sue ] What ? What happened ?
[ Jade ] He smashed his face really bad .
What are you talking about , " smashed his face " ?
- How did he smash his face ? - I don 't know . I don 't know .
I don 't know , I wasn 't in the room !
[ Sue tersely ] Stop crying and tell me what happened .
- Three or four minutes , maybe ? - [ Jade ] I 'm sorry , Mum . [ cries ]
[ Sue ] Jade ! Jade , frickin ' answer me !
[ door opens ]
[ keys clatter ]
Can we talk about this ?
Mia .
Dad , I just want to go to sleep .
Can you tell me one thing ?
We didn 't give him anything .
What happened , then ?
I dunno .
I wish you 'd just be honest with me .
Right , because you 've been so honest with me .
What 's that supposed to mean ?
It means there 's something you haven 't told me about Mum .
Isn 't there ?
Right .
- [ ominous music playing ] - [ breathing shakily ]
[ exhales ]
[ machine whirring and beeping steadily ]
[ knocking at door ]
Tell me he 's okay .
No offense , I don 't want you here right now .
Wait , Jade . Come on .
[ quietly ] Mia .
[ foreboding music playing ]
[ footsteps approaching ]
- Sue , | I ... - Don 't !
What are you doing here ?
I just-I just came to see how he was .
He 's bad , Mia . He 's really fucking bad .
- Did you give him something ? - No .
Come on . I know you 've done shit before . What was it ?
Nothing , I swear .
Look at his face .
What did my son ever do to you ?
[ ... I didn 't hurt him .
Go home . Now .
No , please , can I just see him ?
You come back here , I 'm gonna call the police .
Sue ...
- Jade . - Just go home .
No , Jade , I 'm so sorry ...
[ door closes ]
[ indistinct announcement over PA ]
[ monitor beeping steadily ]
- [ indistinct conversation ] - [ female voice , softly ] Mi ...
[ sinister music playing ]
[ sinister music builds ]
[ door creaking ]
[ door creaks , bangs ]
[ faint scratching ]
[ light flickers ]
Mum ?
[ faint scratching ]
Mum , is that you ?
[ scratching continues ]
- [ female voice ] Help me ! - Mum ?
Mum ?
Mum ? [ grunting ]
- Mum ! - [ female voice ] Mia !
[ breathing shakily ]
[ breathes shakily ]
Mia .
- [ sobbing ] - What 's wrong ?
Are you okay ?
[ sobbing ]
[ rain pattering ]
Was your dad pissed ?
[ sniffles ] Yeah .
I 'm 18 , so the police didn 't call mine .
[ exhales ] They can 't know .
Where do they think you are ?
Cousin 's .
I can 't go home .
They 'll know something 's up .
You can stay at mine .
[ sighs ]
Just ' cause of me and Jade .
It might be ... weird .
Yeah , but ...
we 're just friends . It 's not like it 's illegal or anything .
[ Mia sniffles ]
I just ... I don 't want to be alone .
Okay .
[ thunder rumbling ]
I can 't believe I spoke to her .
[ sighs ] I don 't think that was your mum , Mia .
No , it was at first .
She used to call me " Mi " all the time . I mean , how would the spirits know that ?
I feel like they read what we think , you know ? I mean ...
They were in us .
They could know everything about us .
Or maybe ...
Mum was there because she was trying to reach out .
We could check .
[ exhales ] No . I 'm never doing it again , Mia .
Sorry .
[ sighs ]
[ chuckles ]
Forgot about that . [ chuckles ]
- I was such a loser . - You were cute .
- Remember when we held hands ? - Yeah .
I could feel your heart beating through your fingertips .
Yeah , you paid me out ' cause your hands were bigger than mine .
- And they probably still are . - [ scoffs ] No way .
[ chuckles ]
[ both chuckle ]
It is . You have the tiniest hands .
Yeah , I ... I didn 't do puberty right .
[ siren approaching ]
[ siren stops ]
[ somber music playing ]
[ thunder rumbling ]
[ music becomes unsettling ]
[ playful chatter on recording ]
[ laughter on recording ]
[ playful chatter on recording continues ]
[ Mia on recording ] No , wait , Jade , Jade ...
[ playful chatter and laughter on recording continue ]
[ playful screaming on recording ]
[ recording stops playing ]
Mum .
What 's your message to the haters ?
Suck my arse ! Mm-hmm !
Mum !
Get off me . Get off !
[ laughs ]
Who 's the cutest ?
- [ both ] Me . Me . - Me .
- Who 's the hottest ? - Me .
- Who 's the best ? - [ both ] Me !
- Who 's the funniest ? - [ both ] Me .
- [ both laugh ] - [ Mia ] You suck !
[ both ] You suck !
Fuck the haters !
[ gentle ethereal music playing ]
[ ethereal music fades ]
[ ominous music playing ]
[ thunder rumbling ]
[ distorted soundscape ]
[ distant banging on door ]
[ banging on door continues ]
- [ faint distressed shouting ] - [ banging intensifies ]
[ loud banging on door ]
[ distressed shouting grows louder ]
[ banging continues ]
[ shouting continues ]
[ forceful bang ]
[ distantly ] Please ... no . No , Rhea ...
Rhea ... [ continues faintly ]
[ breathing shakily ]
[ groans softly ]
[ faint scratching ]
[ scratching intensifies ]
- [ scratching stops ] - [ gasps ]
[ panting heavily ]
[ woman humming faintly ]
[ humming stops ]
[ eerie music playing ]
[ woman breathing raggedly ]
[ eerie music builds ]
[ Mia yelps ]
[ woman moaning ]
Daniel ?
[ woman moans ]
Daniel ! Daniel , wake up !
[ screaming ] Daniel , wake up !
Daniel !
Wake up !
Oh , what the ... Mia !
- Stop ! - [ gasps ]
[ stammering ] Where is she ? Oh , my God , oh , my God !
Oh , my God , they followed us . Whoever we contacted , they followed us .
- What are you talking about ? - She was sucking your foot !
You were sucking my feet , Mia . You had my foot in your mouth !
What ? No , I didn 't .
- I 'm gonna go . - Wait , Daniel ...
- Mia , stop ! - No , don 't leave me !
- No , I 'm going . - [ whimpers ] Stay with me .
[ sobbing raggedly ]
[ breathing wheezily ]
[ groans ]
[ sobs , screams ]
[ breathing heavily ]
[ breathing shakily ]
[ screaming hysterically ]
[ sobbing ]
Mum ? [ sobbing ]
[ foreboding music playing ]
Please , please , Mum .
Talk to me .
Mum .
[ gasps ]
Did you ...
did you kill yourself ?
No . Not on purpose , Mi .
Is that the truth ?
I 'd never want to leave you .
Ever .
I 'm here .
Always .
[ water bubbling faintly ]
[ voice deepens ] Mia .
Riley needs help .
[ water bubbling faintly ]
[ faint bubbling continues ]
[ cell phone vibrating ]
Oh , your father . Unbelievable .
[ sighs ] Can you stay with him , Jade ?
[ softly ] Riley .
Riley , please say something .
Riley ?
Riley .
- [ Riley grunts ] - [ Jade shrieks ]
[ Jade grunts ]
[ cries out ]
[ panting rapidly ]
Mum ! Mum !
No , Riley , stop ! Riley , stop !
- [ heavy thudding ] - [ tiles crack ]
Stop ! Stop !
[ laughing ]
- [ laughs maniacally ] - [ Jade ] Stop !
Stop !
[ eerie music playing ]
[ Sue ] Riley !
Oh , shit !
- [ Riley grunting ] - Stop ! Nurse !
Please stop him ! Please stop him !
[ Sue whimpering ]
Riley , fucking stop it !
Won 't you fucking do something !
[ dissonant music playing ]
[ Hayley ] it was you who took it .
You could 've fucking said something , Mia .
- [ Joss ] Who showed the police the video ? - [ Daniel ] Think it was James .
[ Hayley ] At least it proves we didn 't touch him .
Police said there 's not a lot they can do about a kid hitting himself .
- [ Daniel ] Has it ever lasted this long ? - [ Joss ] No .
But we 've never been over 90 seconds before Mia , so ...
[ normal volume ] How is he ?
Every time he comes to , he tries to kill himself .
- [ Joss ] They wanna keep him . - [ Jade ] What ?
The guy who gave Duckett the hand said that if you die while they 're in you ,
they 'll have you forever .
Have any of you guys ... still been seeing stuff ?
What the fuck you mean , " seeing stuff " ?
I saw my Mum at the hospital .
And another one attacked Daniel at my house .
- [ Hayley ] Did you see something ? - [ Daniel ] Uh ... not exactly .
[ Joss ] What 's that supposed to mean , Daniel ?
I woke up and Mia was ...
I dunno ...
sucking my feet .
The fuck ?
- Jade . - What do you mean , " woke up with Mia " ?
What do you mean , " sucking your feet " ?
- It wasn 't me , I swear to God . - I couldn 't go home .
[ Joss ] None of us have been seeing shit , all right ?
And we all did it . We were all there .
So , why would you be seeing your mum ? You didn 't even let her in .
[ Hayley ] Wait , didn 't Duckett say they could imitate people ?
Wait , who 's Duckett ?
I got the hand off him . He , uh ...
I met him twice at some parties and ...
Yeah , we did the hand shit ,
and I asked if I could borrow it and he said I could keep it .
He said he was seeing them without it .
[ Hayley ] And then he went full skitz .
Stabbed his brother , then killed himself .
The brother . Can we talk to him ?
[ Joss ] What 's up , bruz ?
What are you doing here ?
We gotta talk about Duckett .
Yeah .
Do you know what the shit thing is ?
He actually thought he had friends .
You guys always inviting him to shit , acting like you cared .
- But you were using him . - We weren 't using him , Cole .
A real friend would 've seen it was fucking him up .
- But you didn 't . - [ bus idles ]
[ Joss ] Look , bruz , I know it 's a shit time for you right now , but we need your help .
Nah , man , I 'm out .
[ exhales ] Cole .
[ low indistinct chatter ]
[ bus door closes ]
I know how much it hurts to lose someone that close .
The people he let in messed up his head .
If he 'd just stopped doing that fucking thing , they would 've left .
[ Jade ] My little brother 's in hospital . He went way over .
You let a kid do it ?
His body should kick ' em out . They get weaker the longer they 're in .
- It hasn 't . - Give it time .
They 're killing him .
Maybe it 's time you stop fucking up people 's lives , Joss .
What do you reckon ?
Jade !
Jade , just wait ! Jade !
- You shouldn 't have let him do it , Mia ! - We all decided it 'd be okay .
- [ Hayley ] We didn 't decide anything . - We did . We all said ...
We didn 't say shit , Mia . That was just you .
And then you let it go for two minutes .
- Jade - - - And then you sleep with my boyfriend .
What the fuck is wrong with you ?
- Jade , it wasn 't like that . - Of course , you 're gonna take her side .
[ exhales ]
Jesus ...
I wish that you didn 't force yourself into my family , Mia .
[ Mia tearfully ] Um ...
Did we blow the candle out ?
[ Joss ] I don 't remember .
What if we opened the door but we didn 't shut it ?
What are you saying ?
I 'm saying we do it again with Riley , but blow out the candle this time .
You want him to do it again ? The thing that put him in hospital ?
- You wanna save him ? - Don 't fucking ask me that .
Well , we have to do something , Jade !
[ sighs ]
[ tense music playing ]
I 'll give it back after , okay ?
Just burn the fuckin ' thing .
Hey , good luck .
[ cell phone ringing and vibrating ]
[ sniffles ]
Mum 's back in , like , an hour .
We 'll be quick .
[ respirator pulsing steadily ]
[ unsettling music playing ]
Oh , my God .
[ Velcro snaps ]
[ match strikes ]
[ Mia ] Come on , Riley . Come on , please .
Talk to him .
[ Riley breathing steadily ]
Okay , yeah , blow it out .
[ Daniel ] Anything ?
I don 't know . Um ...
Maybe if we just try it again .
- [ Jade ] Mia ... - Just try it again .
[ matches rattling ]
[ match strikes ]
[ Mia ] Talk to him .
[ Daniel ] It 's not working .
[ Mia ] Okay . Um ...
What if I use the hand to speak to him ?
- [ Jade ] No . - What ? He 's not dead , Mi .
No , but what if his spirit is disconnected from his body or something ?
- I thought these spirits were in limbo . - Yeah , well , maybe that 's where Riley is .
- Might not be him . - Well , what if it is ?
- And what if it isn 't ? - Yeah , this is a bad idea , Mia .
[ Jade ] Mia .
Mia , don 't .
[ breathing deeply ]
Riley , talk to me .
[ breathing shakily ]
Hi .
- [ Jade ] Is it him ? - Shh .
Is there a boy here ?
Him .
Do you know where he is ?
Please .
I can take you to him .
Okay .
I let you in .
[ gasping ]
[ guttural screaming and clamoring ]
[ screaming ] Help !
[ screaming and clamoring intensify ]
[ screaming and clamoring stop ]
[ groans ]
- [ Mia sobbing ] - Hey . Hey , hey , hey . You okay ?
No ! Don 't touch me !
[ sobbing ] Don 't touch me !
Hey , hey , hey .
Hey .
- It 's just us . - [ sobs ]
It 's just me and Daniel .
- What happened ? - [ sobbing ] I saw him .
They 're hurting him , Jade .
They 're not gonna stop .
They 're never gonna stop .
[ Mia screams ]
[ Mia screaming in anguish ]
[ Mia mutters ]
[ distorted scream echoing ]
[ screaming continues ]
[ Max ] Mia .
I haven 't been completely honest with you .
But I want to be .
Your mother ...
before she passed , she left us something .
Something I 've been scared to show you , which is ... which is wrong of me .
Because it 's ... it 's just as much as yours as it is mine .
Can I read it to you ?
" Dear Max and Mia .
It is Tuesday today and it 's raining .
It 's the first time in a long time I haven 't felt hopeless . "
[ inhales ]
" In fact ...
I am full of hope .
I hope you live beyond your years
and find absolute happiness .
I hope you ... I hope you don 't hate me for this . "
[ voice catches ]
" I hope you find it in your heart to forgive me .
I hope you can find some peace in knowing
I am no longer in pain . "
[ Max sobbing ]
I 'm sorry , Mi .
- It 's hers , Mia . - No .
- Mm-mm . Mm-mm . - It 's okay .
No , she didn 't do it .
She didn 't do it , because she told me , Dad .
She didn 't do it , because she told me .
[ Mia sniffles ]
[ sobbing ] She told me . She told me .
- Mia . - [ sobbing ]
Mia . Come here .
Sweetheart .
- [ Mia sniffles ] - She 's gone .
I 'm sorry I kept it from you .
[ sniffling ]
I didn 't want you blaming yourself .
[ faint scratching ]
[ Rhea ] It 's not true .
- I 'll be back . - What ?
- I 'll be back , I promise . - Mi ...
I promise . I just ... I just gotta go .
I 'll be back , Dad . I 'll be back .
[ continues sobbing ]
[ Rhea ] Mi .
He 's lying .
- Then why did you write it ? - I didn 't .
Sweetheart .
That 's not your dad .
[ shakily ] What ?
[ footsteps approaching ]
[ Max 's voice ] Mia ?
[ banging on door ]
That 's not Max .
- [ Max 's voice ] Mia ? - They 're imitating him .
- [ banging on door ] - [ doorknob rattling ]
He 's going to hurt you .
- [ whimpers ] - [ Max 's voice ] Mia , open the door !
[ banging on door intensifies ]
- [ banging continues ] - [ Rhea ] Riley can 't stay there .
- [ Max 's voice ] Mia ? - He 's suffering , Mi .
[ whimpering ] What ... what do I do ?
[ banging continues ]
He needs to die .
- What ? - [ Max 's voice ] Mia ?
You have to put him out of his misery .
No , Mum , I-I-I can 't . I can 't .
They 're never gonna let him go .
- [ shouting , banging continue ] - No , Mum , please , no ...
I 'll look after him , Mi .
[ Max 's voice , shouting ] Open the damn door !
Help him , Mia .
- [ Max 's voice ] Let me in ! - [ Riley gasping ]
- Help him , Mia ! - [ banging intensifies ]
No , just leave me alone !
[ gasping ]
[ panting weakly ]
- [ grunting ] - [ Mia yelps ]
[ Mia straining ]
[ chokes ]
- [ Mia gasps for air ] - [ Max ] Mia !
- Mia ! - Help me !
[ grunting ]
I 'm trying !
[ thumping on door ]
- [ thumping continues ] - [ Max grunting ]
[ tense music builds ]
Mia !
[ grunts ]
[ panting ]
[ somber music playing ]
[ scissors clatter ]
- Oh , my God . - [ thudding ]
[ quiet spluttering ]
[ breathing heavily ]
[ " Crazy Frog " ringtone playing ]
[ cell phone beeps ]
- [ Jade ] Hey . - Jade ?
You okay ?
I know what to do .
We can save him .
[ exhales ]
You know , I actually think he 's getting better .
He woke up for a second . It 's like he was himself again .
I 've seen him , Jade .
He 's in pain .
And every second is agony for him .
[ uneasy music playing ]
Just come to mine .
- And I 'll show you . - Show me what ?
You just have to be here , Jade .
Please .
- Just trust me . - [ sighs ] Oh , shit .
Okay . I 'll be there in ten .
[ cell phone beeps ]
[ car engine starts ]
[ menacing music playing ]
- Mia . - [ gasps ]
I 'm ... sorry .
No , it 's okay . Sit .
I was wondering when I 'd see you again .
You haven 't come .
You told me not to .
Yeah , I know . I was mad .
You had every right to be .
Still do .
No , I don 't .
There were no drugs , Mia .
[ Sue exhales ]
He had a breakdown . I just ... I just ...
couldn 't face that .
I 'm so sorry that I blamed you . I know that you wouldn 't do anything to hurt him .
I love you guys .
You 're not Riley 's friend , Mia , you 're his family .
It 'd mean so much to him that you were here .
Can I have a minute with him ?
- Alone . - Of course .
[ door opens ]
[ honking ]
[ cell phone unlocks , beeps ]
[ cell phone vibrating ]
[ vibrating continues ]
I 'm so sorry .
[ line ringing ]
[ sighs ]
- [ ominous music builds ] - [ liquid trickling ]
[ gasps ]
[ ominous music intensifies ]
[ bed rattling ]
[ whimpers ]
- [ bed rattling ] - [ chuckling softly ]
[ guttural voice ] Found me .
Mia !
I am ending this !
[ guttural voice ] You ... can 't take him .
He 's ours .
[ soft cackling ]
Where is he ?
You saw .
[ shrieking ]
[ breathes heavily , strains ]
[ sobbing ]
[ guttural voice ] Why don 't you ...
touch me ?
I want to feel you .
[ animal grunting ]
[ kangaroo groans ]
[ echoing screams ]
[ kangaroo grunts ]
[ echoing screams continue ]
Max ?
[ elevator dings ]
Jade . Where are you ?
[ Jade on phone ] At Mia 's . She 's not here .
- Max needs an ambulance . - What ... No , Mia 's here .
What 's wrong ? What 's happened ?
- She 's there ? - Yeah , she 's with Riley .
Mum , she 's dangerous !
Mia ?
Riley !
[ urgent music playing ]
Hey ! Where 's my son ? He was in this room .
Well , he should be here . He was just here .
Well , where the fuck is he ?
[ tires screech ]
[ ominous music builds ]
Mia !
Mia ! Riley .
[ traffic roaring ]
- [ traffic roaring ] - [ horns blare ]
[ Jade ] Riley !
Mia , stop !
Mia !
[ vehicles rushing by ]
[ gentle ethereal music playing ]
[ whispers ] I 'm so proud of you .
[ cackling weakly ]
Take him , my darling girl .
You 're doing the right thing .
Mm-hmm .
- Show him the way . - [ sniffles ]
[ Rhea ] I can protect him .
We 'll have him forever .
Riley !
- [ music playing on radio ] - [ tires screech ]
- [ heavy thud ] - [ tires squeal ]
[ man ] Oh ...
[ dissonant eerie music playing ]
[ distorted soundscape ]
[ man ] Did you see what happened ?
[ muffled , frantic chatter ]
[ Jade whispering ] It 's okay .
[ distorted soundscape continues ]
Riley ?
[ Sue speaking indistinctly ]
- I 'm gonna be so far behind . - Don 't worry about it .
- [ conversation fades ] - [ distortion intensifies ]
Dad ?
Dad !
Wait , Dad !
[ loud clang ]
Jade ? Sue ?
[ breathing heavily ]
- Dad ? - [ loud clanging ]
Dad !
- Dad , wait ! - [ clanging continues ]
Oh , Dad !
- Dad , wait ! - [ distortion swells , fades ]
[ screaming ] Don 't leave me !
Please !
[ Mia sobbing ]
[ match strikes ]
[ eerie droning music playing ]
[ eerie droning music intensifies ]
- [ music stops abruptly ] - [ gasps ]
[ man breathing heavily ]
[ speaks Greek ]
[ man breathing shakily ]
- [ in English ] I let you in . - [ gasps ]
♪ I saw God in a body bag
♪ I got lost in the stars when they 'd cross like a polygraph ♪
♪ Never lie , cardiac in every line
♪ Insomniac forever , never go to sleep again ♪
♪ Black lungs from the falling ash ♪
♪ Giraffe tongue with a heart to match ♪
♪ Get sawed in half like the Dahlia ♪
♪ Place pain on display in Hollywood ♪
♪ Paint it all like Dali would Face of War ♪
♪ Fountain pens melting , countenances in a drawing book ♪
♪ A psycho full of cyclones , eyes closed ♪
♪ 1 go cold when I fly low , brains feed on haikus
♪ Isolated in my temples , Cairo ♪
♪ Bones jut from their homes like they 're silos ♪
♪ I 'm Silent Hill , tell me where the time went ♪
♪ Kill Pyramids that followed with the knife gripped ♪
♪ Vice-grips always on the mind when the crisis hits ♪
♪ Everywhere it 's like a mine I step ♪
♪ I 'm an atom bomb made of atoms ♪
♪ Add ' em up , Adam 's apple 's rotten ♪
♪ Smashed to apple sauce , adamant ♪
♪ No Adam Eve in anatomy ♪
♪ Only albatrosses if I have to speak ♪
♪ Another casualty of the casted wings
♪ Casually I 'm high again ♪
♪ Vibrant as a hyacinth idling ♪
♪ So I pretend that my defense is working ♪
♪ Lurking with the burdens that still hide below the surface
♪ I know these things have meaning ♪
Sometimes I don 't know the purpose , introverted ♪
♪ Dizzy from the disconcerted tizzies ♪
♪ Mr. Perfect isn 't worth it , give me what I didn 't earn ♪
♪ Put it in an urn , live and learn ♪
♪ I could never tell the difference ♪
♪ When I 'm miniature red alerts ♪
♪ Read aloud like ministers ♪
♪ It 's hard to breathe when you 're drowning in the goodbyes ♪
But I 'm still here now , so tell me what that look like ♪
♪ They use a sword to signify that you 're a good Knight ♪
♪ Then use the same one to kill you and say goodnight ♪
♪ Goodnight , goodnight , goodnight , goodnight ... ♪
[ atmospheric music outro ]
[ song fades out ]
[ eerie instrumental music playing ]
[ music fades out ]